[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a weak password?",
        "choices": ["A) ILoveYou123", "B) P@ssw0rd", "C) 123456", "D) All of the above"],
        "answer": "D) All of the above"
    },

    {    
        
        "question": "What is a common method to improve the security of online accounts?",
        "choices": ["A) Keeping passwords written down on sticky notes", "B) Enabling two-factor authentication", "C) Sharing passwords with friends and family", "D)  Using the same password for multiple accounts"],
        "answer": "B) Enabling two-factor authentication"

    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is a type of antivirus program?",
        "choices": ["A) Norton", "B) Mcafee", "C) Kaspersky", "D) All of the above"],
        "answer": "D) All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following describes the process for verifying the integrity of a message?",
        "choices": ["A) Decryption algorithm", "B) Digital signature", "C) Protocol", "D) Message Digest"],
        "answer": "D) Message Digest"
    },
    {
        "question": "To protect the computer system against hackers and viruses, what is an essential tool to always keep on in the computer system?",
        "choices": ["A) Firewall", "B) Antivirus", "C) Script", "D) Vlc player"],
        "answer": "A) Firewall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of a VPN?",
        "choices": ["A) Blocks access to certain websites", "B) Acts as a firewall", "C) Encrypts internet traffic to protect data and privacy ", "D) Increases internet speed"],
        "answer": "C)  Encrypts internet traffic to protect data and privacy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the initial step to take when responding to a cybersecurity incident?",
        "choices": ["A) Contacting the media", "B)  Immediately paying any demanded ransom", "C) Ignoring the incident and hoping it goes away", "D) Reporting the incident to the proper authorities"],
        "answer": "D) Reporting the incident to the proper authorities"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can be considered as the elements of cyber security?",
        "choices": ["A) Operational Security", "B) All the displayed options", "C) Network Security", "D) Application Security"],
        "answer": "B) All the displayed options"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do hackers usually use computer viruses?",
        "choices": ["A) To log, monitor each and every user's stroke", "B) To gain access the sensitive information like user's Id and Passwords", "C) To log, monitor each and every user's stroke", "D) All of the above"],
        "answer": "D) All of the above"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "In cybersecurity, what is encryption?",
        "choices": ["A) The process of monitoring and analyzing network traffic for potential security threats", "B) The process of physically securing a computer system to prevent tampering", "C) The process of encoding information in such a way that only authorized parties can access it", "D) The process of updating software to fix security vulnerabilities"],
        "answer": "C) The process of encoding information in such a way that only authorized parties can access it"
    }
    
    
]
